Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1925-1984; Series I; 15.5; (31 boxes)
  - Dent, Peter
    - "The castle wall," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 638)
    - "Celebration," typescript, 1966 Feb (Box 10, Folder 639)
    - "Children at Bournemouth, 1945," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 640)
    - [Reviews] A Cornered Freedom, by Christopher Hampton and The Hollow Places, by I. P. Taylor, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 641)
    - "The Crowd," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 642)
    - [Review] "David Miller. The Caryatids ," typescript, with a note, 1975 Sep 22 (Box 10, Folder 643)
    - [Review] "Douglas Dunn The Happier Life ," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 644)
    - "Draft for VI, A Response," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 645)
    - "Elixir," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 646)
    - "Far from the crowd," typescript, 1966 Mar 29 (Box 10, Folder 647)
    - "Focus Germanus: a sequence," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 648)
    - " from Scarlet Beads," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 649)
    - "The girl," typescript, 2c., 1966 Feb (Box 10, Folder 650)
    - "Holdings" and "Drift," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 651)
    - "Ignition," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 652)
    - "In passing," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 653)
    - [Review]"John Stallworthy: The Apple Barrel: Selected Poems 1956-1963 "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 654)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 655)
    - [Review] ' Kipling, Auden & Co essays and reviews, by Randall Jarrell," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 656)
    - "The letters," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 657)
    - "Light," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 658)
    - "Mine," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 659)
    - "Momentum," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 660)
    - "Morning Air"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 661)
      - Page Proof, undated (Box 10, Folder 662)
    - "Pickings" and "Wave," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 663)
    - "Plans," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 664)
    - "Poems and Versions After the Sanskit," typescript, 2c., undated (Box 10, Folder 665)
      With: ANS to Peter [Dale] from Peter D[ent], undated
    - "Prunus subhirtella pendula rubra (Flowering cherry)," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 666)
    - "Recent and Revised Poems - Unpublished," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 667)
    - "Reflection," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 668)
    - "Respite," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 669)
    - "The Route," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 670)
    - "St. Bernard's Convent," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 671)
    - "Scene," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 672)
    - [Review] "Seamus Heaney: North ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 673)
    - [Seven Chinese Poems]: typescript, 1982 Apr (Box 10, Folder 674)
    - "The Snow," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 675)
    - "Stealth" and "Storm," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 676)
    - "Still Life" and "Night Sky," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 677)
    - "Storm," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 678)
    - "Three Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 679)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 680)
    - "To F.C.," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 681)
    - "To Reverend T.C.," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 682)
    - [Review] "Tom Scott Brand the Builder ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 683)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 684)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 685)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1975 Feb 22 (Box 10, Folder 686)
        With: ALS to William [Cookson] from Peter Dent, 1975 Feb 22
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 687)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 688)
    - "The water's edge," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 689)
    - "Withdrawal," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 690)
    - ["Versions from the Chinese",] typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 691)
    - "Verticals," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 692)
    - Untitled article, galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 693)
    - Untitled collection of poems, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 694)
  - Desnos, Robert
    - "Three Poems," typescript, (1936, 1945, undated) (Box 10, Folder 695)
  - Dodds, Ian
    - "Family," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 696)
    - "Piccadilly, Manchester," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 697)
  - Dodsworth, Martin
    - "Donald Davie"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 698)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 699)
  - Doinas, Stefan Aug.
    - "The Ascent," typescript, 2c., undated (Box 10, Folder 700)
    - "Two Poems," translated by Virgil Nemoianu and Peter Jay, typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 701)
  - Dondo, Mathurin
    - "Histoire Naturelle Poémes," galley, with author's corrections, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 702)
  - Du Bouchet, André
    - "Cable," translated by David Gascoyne, typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 703)
  - Dubnov, Eugene
    See: John Heath-Stubbs
  - Dumitrescu, Geo
    - "Dancing," translated by Dan Dutescu, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 704)
    - "I Could Show How the Grass Grows," translated by Dan Dutescu, typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 705)
  - Duncan, Ronald
    - "Arse for Arse Sake," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 706)
    - "Letter to Ezra," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 707)
    - "Lute Song for Rose Marie," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 708)
    - "No. 12," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 709)
    - "Ode to Ignorance," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 710)
    - "Part III," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 711)
    - "Plain Song," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 712)
    - "The Plea," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 713)
    - "Sent to a Mr. Coe on Bromo," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 714)
    - "Solitude No. 48," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 715)
    - "The Solitudes - No.7," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 716)
    - "The Testament," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 717)
    - Untitled article, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 718)
    - Untitled poem, typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 719)
  - Dunmore, Helen
    - "Patrick," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 720)
  - Dwyer, Frank
    - "Agon," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 721)
    - "Eurynome," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 722)
    - "Magic for the Montebank," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 723)
    - "Over the Edge," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 724)
  - Eagleton, Terry
    - "The Poetry of Peter Dale"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 725)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 726)
  - Eastman, Barbara
    - "The Gap in the Cantos: 72 and 73"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 727)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, 2c., undated (Box 11, Folder 728)
  - Eberhart, Richard
    - [Response to the Agenda questionnaire], galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 729)
      With: TLS to William Cookson from Richard Eberhart, 1973 Sep 17
    - "Wild Life and Tamed Life," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 730)
  - Edwards, Michael
    - "The Poetry of Charles Tomlinson," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 731)
  - Eluard, Paul
    - "Humphrey Jennings," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 732)
  - Estep, Robert
    - "L' Abbatage," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 733)
    - "Charlemagne Before Ygdrasil," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 734)
    - "Death of Wat Tyler," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 735)
    - "The Empty Vase," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 736)
    - "The Four Queens," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 737)
    - "Hunt by Night," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 738)
    - "An Image of Lethe," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 739)
    - "The King of Salem," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 740)
    - "The Laws," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 741)
    - "Venus of the Rocks," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 742)
    - "Vestiges," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 743)
    - "Wands and Pentagons," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 744)
    - "Yoshitsune's Flight," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 745)
  - Evans, Gregory
    - "Daniel," printed version, in French and English, undated (Box 11, Folder 746)
  - Evans, Ruth
    - "Ashley," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 747)
    - "Daughter," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 748)
  - Ewart, Gavin
    - "On Seeing Lord Longford From the Top of a London Bus," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 749)
  - Feng, Hs'ueh-feng (Feng Xuefeng)
    - "The Morning Glow," "The Unfortunate" and "When Water Comes Downhill," unidentifed translator, printed version, undated (Box 11, Folder 750)
  - Ferguson, Peter
    - "Philip Larkin's XX Poems: The Missing Link"
      - Typescript, original draft, undated (Box 11, Folder 751)
        With: TLS to William Cookson from Peter Ferguson, 1976 May 3
      - Typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 752)
      - Typescript, revised version, undated (Box 11, Folder 753)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, [1976] (Box 11, Folder 754)
      - Galley, undated (Box 11, Folder 755)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert
    - "Mirroring the Commedia. An Appreciation of Laurence Binyon's Version: typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 756)
  - Fleming, William
    - "Definitions Towards a Note on Civilization," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 757)
  - Follain, Jean
    - "Amour," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 758)
    - "Fantômes de la Ville," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 759)
    - "Sixteen Poems," translated by Clare Sheppard
      - Typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 760)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 761)
    - "Ten Poems," translated by F. Giles
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 762)
      - Galley, undated (Box 11, Folder 763)
  - Fone, Stefanie
    - "Conversation Piece. After the Journey"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 764)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 765)
  - Ford, Ford Maddox
    - "On Ezra Pound's Cathay, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 766)
  - Frenaud, André
    - "The Magi," translated by Keith Bosley
      - Printed version, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 767)
      - Galley, with corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 768)
  - Fu, Hsüan (Fu Xuan)
    - "Of Time," translated by John Cayley, typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 769)
  - Fu, T'ien-lin (Fu Tianlin)
    - "Fallen Leaves," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 11, Folder 770)
    - "To My Child," translated by Hu Shiguang, printed version, undated (Box 11, Folder 771)
  - Fuller, Buckminster
    - [Review] Ezra Pound and Music: The Complete Criticism, galley, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 772)
    - "Pound, Synergy, and the Great Design," galley, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 773)
  - Fuller, Roy
    - "At T. S. Eliot's Memorial Service: 4.iii.1965," typescript, 1965 Mar 4 (Box 11, Folder 774)
    - Untitled article, galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 11, Folder 775)
  - Fulton, Robin
    - "the distance between the two," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 776)
    - "keeping his balance," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 777)
    - "a lifework," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 778)
    - [Review] "Michael Hamburger's German Translations," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 779)
      With: TLS to William Cookson from Robin Fulton, 1978 Mar 27, and "Bertolt Brecht" and "Paul Celan," by Olav Hauge, translated by Robin Fulton
    - "on a poem by Sereni," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 780)
    - "peace at last," typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 781)
  - Gall, Sally M.
    - "Domestic Monologues: The Problem of Voice Poetry," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 782)
  - Gatsos, Nikos
    - "Song of the Old Days," translated by Peter Levi, typescript, corrected, 1968 Sep 29 (Box 12, Folder 783)
  - Gheorghe, Ion
    - "Fragment," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 784)
  - Giardelli, Arthur
    - "Three related works by David Jones"
      - Printed version, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 785)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 786)
    - "Trystan Ac Esyllt"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 787)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 788)
  - Gibbens, John
    - "The Laying on of Words"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 789)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 790)
  - Gibbons, Reginald
    - "As is the Custom," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 791)
    - "Blocked" and "Welfare," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 792)
    - "The Flaw" and "To L. B. Dead Five Years," printed version, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 793)
    - "Half Asleep at Midnight, Upstairs, on the Coast, in a Storm," galley, with author's corrections, photocopy, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 794)
    - "In Memoriam E. L. P.," printed version, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 795)
    - "Lentils," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 796)
    - "Metamorphoses of a Sonnet by Góngora," printed version, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 797)
    - "Pound and the Gods"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 798)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 799)
    - "Puyé Cliffs"
      - Typescript, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 800)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 801)
        With: TLS to Michael Collier from Reginald Gibbons, 1977 Feb 3
    - "The Sleighbells Fade," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 802)
    - "To a Woman in Bed" and "An Archaeology of the Future," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 803)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 804)
      - Galley, undated (Box 12, Folder 805)
    - "Welfare," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 806)
    - "The Years," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 807)
    - "You Are Insatiable," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 808)
  - Gifford, Henry
    - "Hardy's Revisions"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 809)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 810)
  - Giles, F.
    - "Regionalism: Three Overlooked Poets"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 811)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 812)
        See also: John Surple
  - Gill, David
    - "Translators," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 813)
  - Glaser, Elton
    - "Escape Artist" and "The Bath," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 814)
    - "Farmlife in Ohio," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 815)
    - "from Brief Songs, typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 816)
      With: TLS to Michael Collier from Elton Glasser, 1976 Dec 20
    - "Half-Thawed Poem" and "Tense in the Perennial Present," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 817)
    - "Hunting Song of the Kayak-paddler," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 818)
    - "The Middle Way," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 819)
    - "A Prognathous," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 820)
    - "The Touch"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 821)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 822)
        With: ALS to "Editors" from Elton Glasser, 1977 Feb 3
  - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang Von
    - "Seven Poems," translated by Michael Hamburger, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 823)
  - Goldfarb, Sidney
    - "Three Poems"
      - Typescript and printed version, undated (Box 12, Folder 824)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 825)
  - Gordon, D. M.
    - "The Cyclops-Ideogram," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 826)
      With: TL to [William] Cookson from [D. M. Gordon], 1959 Dec 7
  - Gowrie, Grey
    - "Editorial," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 827)
    - "Grey Gowrie Writes," holograph and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 828)
    - "Peter Dale"
      - Holograph, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 829)
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 830)
  - Grass, Günter
    - "Orpheus," [translated by Michael Hamburger,] typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 831)
    - "Sixty-Six," [translated by Michael Hamburger] typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 832)
    - "Sleepless," translated by Michael Hamburger, typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 833)
    - "The Steam Boiler Effect," translated by Michael Hamburger, typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 834)
    - "Vermont," [translated by Michael Hamburger], typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 835)
  - Greening, John
    - "Peter Huchel"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 836)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 837)
  - Griffin, Jonathan
    - "Michael Hamburger, Poet and Poet's Critic," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 838)
  - Grisewood, Harman
    - "René Hague. Died 19th January. 1981. An Address at the Requiem Mass, Westminster Cathedral, March 13, 1981," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 839)
  - Grover, Philip
    - "'Provincia Deserta' and the Concept of the Past on Pound's Poetry"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 840)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 841)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 842)
  - Gross, Philip
    - "A Survivor," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 843)
  - Gryphius, Andreas
    - "Sonnet," translated by C. H. Sisson, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 844)
  - Guest, Harry
    - "The Dusts," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 845)
    - "Encounter," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 846)
    - "Form," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 847)
    - "Lines For a Bygone Countess or September already - how ever shall we get through the winter here ?" typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 848)
    - "Sonnet," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 849)
  - Gunn, Thom
    - "Bringing to Light," typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 850)
    - "Hardy and the Ballads"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 851)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 852)
  - Gurney, John
    - "Christopher Fry: A Sleep of Prisoners- Growth, or Confusion of Vision?" typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 853)
    - [Review] The Hollow Landscapes, by William Bedford
      - Typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 854)
      - Galley, corrected, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 855)
    - "Soldiers"
      - Typescript, annotated, undated (Box 12, Folder 856)
      - Galley, undated (Box 12, Folder 857)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 12, Folder 858)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 859)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 860)
  - Hadrian, Emperor of Rome
    - "The Apocryphal Poems of Hadrian," unidentified translator, typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 861)
  - Hagiu, Gregore
    - "Pigeons in a Belfry," translated by Vera Lungu
      - Holograph and typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 862)
  - Hague, René
    - "The Clarity of David Jones," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 863)
    - "The continuation of The Kensington Mass, [Agenda Editions] typescript, 2c., undated (Box 13, Folder 864)
    - "The Death of Hector. A Version After Iliad XXII"
      - Printed version, undated (Box 13, Folder 865)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 866)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 867)
    - "Myth and Mystery in the Poetry of David Jones"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 868)
      - Typescript, incomplete, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 869)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 870)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 871)
      - Galley, fragment, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 872)
        With: ALS to William [Cookson] from René [Hague], 1977 Jul 27
  - Haines, John
    - "Deserted Cabin," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 873)
  - Hale, Christopher
    - [Reviews] "Hippopotamus Press," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 874)
  - Hall, Donald
    - "Old Roses," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 875)
  - Halperin, Mark
    - "Afterimage," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 876)
    - "Hailstorm," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 877)
    - "A Man Drowning," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 878)
    - "Polestar," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 879)
    - "Such Thin Trees," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 880)
    - "Three Poems," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 881)
      With: TLS to William Cookson from Mark Helperin, 1977 Feb 11
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 882)
    - "Winter Solstice: The Magi," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 883)
  - Hamburger, Michael
    - "Adamic," typescript, corrected, photocopy, undated (Box 13, Folder 884)
    - "Feeding the Chickadees," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 885)
    - "Four Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 886)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 887)
    - [Review] "George Oppen: Collected Poems ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 888)
    - "Gratulatory Variation for Basil Bunting With An Inaudible Ground-Bass, Growled," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 889)
    - "In Massachusetts II," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 890)
    - [Reviews] "János Pilinszky: Selected Poems " and "Edwin Morgan: Rites of Passage ," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 891)
    - "A Jumble of Notes on Myth"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 892)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 893)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 894)
    - "Orpheus Street, S. E. 5," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 895)
    - [Review] " The Sinking of the Titanic. A Poem. By Hans Magnus Enzensberger," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 896)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 897)
    - "Travelling I-V"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 898)
      - Galley, undated (Box 13, Folder 899)
    - "Travelling VI"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 900)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1974 Jun 15 (Box 13, Folder 901)
    - "Travelling VIII," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 902)
    - "Travelling IX," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 903)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 904)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 905)
    - "Variations: In Suffolk"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 906)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 907)
        With: ALS to William [Cookson] from Michael [Hamburger], 1979 Jul 20
    - "Variations: In Suffolk VII"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 908)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1980 Sep 1 (Box 13, Folder 909)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 910)
    - "Vehicles II," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 911)
    - [Reviews] "William Bronk: Silence and Metaphor, Light and Dark, Cid Corman: Once and For All: Poems for William Bronk ," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 912)
    - Untitled article, undated (Box 13, Folder 913)
  - H[amburger?], M[ichael?]
    - [Review] "W. H. Auden: Forewards and Afterwords ," typescript, undated (Box 13, Folder 914)
  - Hamilton, Ian